rockislandauction.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy

Rock Island Auction Company values you as our client and recognizes that privacy is important to you. We want you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose data.

This Privacy Statement describes the privacy practices of Rock Island Auction Company for data that we collect:

  * Through websites operated by us from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, including RockIslandAuction.com and other websites owned or controlled by Rock Island Auction Company (collectively, the “Websites”);
  * Through our social media pages that we control from which you are accessing this Privacy Statement (collectively, our “Social Media Pages”);
  * Through HTML-formatted email messages that we send you that link to this Privacy Statement and through your communications with us; and,
  * When you visit or bid at one of our online or in-person auctions, or through other offline interactions.

Collectively, we refer to the Websites and our Social Media Pages, as the “Online Services” and, together with offline channels described above, the “Services.” By using the Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement.

By visiting [www.RockIslandAuction.com](http://www.rockislandauction.com/) and any related websites you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE GATHER**

Our goal in collecting visitor information online is to provide the best website experience possible, through delivering relevant information that meets user needs.

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but, by choosing to not provide such information, you might not be able to take advantage of certain features on our website. We also receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use cookies, and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our company websites.

**REGISTERING FOR EMAIL UPDATES**

Your email address will not be sold or shared with outside companies. By signing up for our weekly email newsletter, or our auction alerts, you will be notified of special events and may be offered products for sale, including our catalogs.  Should you ever wish to remove your name from our email list, simply click the unsubscribe link.

**INFORMATION WE SHARE WITH OTHERS**

Any personal information you provide to us on our website when you register for emails, make a bid, or submit a request for information is maintained in private files on a secure Web server. Rock Island Auction Company shares this information only with affiliated companies in order to help us provide better service to you. These affiliates are required to maintain your information in the strictest confidence.

We may also share non-personally identifiable information with third party companies to help manage and optimize our online website and email communications, to process payment, and to ensure compliance with government regulations.

As we continue to develop Rock Island Auction Company, we might sell, buy, or create new businesses. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing privacy notice. Also, in the unlikely event that Rock Island Auction Company is acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our auction and collection policies, and enforce purchase, consignment, or other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of [www.RockIslandAuction.com](http://www.rockislandauction.com/), our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.  We do not sell our clients’ information.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

When using links found on our site to other websites not affiliated with Rock Island Auction Company, please be aware those sites have their own privacy policies, which may be different from our own. Also, Rock Island Auction Company is not responsible for services or products that are offered on these websites.

**USE OF COOKIES**

Cookies are used on this website to collect non-personally identifiable visitor information. This information allows us to customize your experience on our website and is used internally to track site usage and provide business insight regarding how users utilize content on the website. This allows us to improve the content and design of our website.

The Rock Island Auction Company websites uses or may use gifs, cookies and reverse IP technology to collect non-personal information regarding use of our sites including, but not limited to: pages read, content downloaded, product interest, demographics, interests, time spent, frequency of visits, the service provider, operating system and IP address. Cookies are a small numeric identifier known as a Unique Visitor Cookie which differentiates one user from another. Users are identified only by a randomly assigned number, not by personally identifiable information.

If you do not wish to have a cookie on your system, you can modify your browser settings to disable cookies.

** ** **CHANGING EMAIL PREFERENCES**

If you provide us your email address for email updates or when you make an online bid, your email address will be added to our guestbook and you will receive email updates and auction alerts via email.

To change your email address in our system or ask to be removed from our system, please email us your request to [info@RockIslandAuction.com](mailto:info@RockIslandAuction.com).

**SECURITY**

Keeping your information secure is important to us, which is why we use a secure server and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

When using the online auction part of our website, your computer will automatically begin to communicate with our server in secure mode. SSL technology encrypts your personal information during the bidding and purchase process, to protect it from being read by others during online transmittal.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**POLICY CHANGES**

From time to time, Rock Island Auction Company may update its Privacy Notice. Please be aware that whenever a change is made, the updated Privacy Notice will be posted on this site.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Notice, please contact us at the address below:

Rock Island Auction Company  
7819 42nd Street West  
Rock Island, Ilinois 61201  
USA  

1.800.238.8022
